Audrey Crockett

Data Scientist

Location Saint Louis, MO

Phone (865) 228-9412

E-mail acrockett@syr.edu

LinkedIn audreymcrockett



Data Science master's graduate with 18 months experience working in radiation oncology bioinformatics, who would like to leverage her for experience as a social scientist and mental health therapist to communicate data outcomes effectively and assist clients with making data informed decisions.

Experience

2018 - present	Data Scientist Mosaic Community Services
2016 - 2017	Clinical Therapist Mosaic Community Services
2015 - 2016	Supervisor of Admissions Powell Recovery Center
2013 - 2015	Clinical Therapist Behavioral Health Partners of Frederick
2011 - 2014	Research Assistant Frostburg State University

Education

2018 - 2019	Syracuse University, Master's of Applied Data Science
2011 - 2014	Frostburg State University - Master's of Counseling Psychology
2008 - 2010	University of Tennessee - Bachelor's of Science - Psychology

Skills

Python

SQL

Intermediate